A girl sits on a bed, focused on her laptop.
Raindrops begin to pour against the window.
Suddenly, a loud explosion is heard.
She turns around, startled by the noise.
The rain continues to fall as thunder rumbles.
The girl stands up, walking towards the window.
Outside, the rain pours heavily onto the plants.
She seems captivated by the view.
A close-up shows her smiling gently.
She appears to enjoy being in the rain.
Next, she's shown putting on a raincoat.
The sounds of the rain persist.
She steps into bright yellow rain boots.
The camera focuses on her feet planting on the floor.
She walks confidently outside.
The view shifts to show her leaving the house.
Rain continues to soak everything around.
As she steps on the porch, she pauses.
She looks thrilled and ready for adventure.
The screen fades to black with a sound of drizzle.
```